(Amy(to Penny, on other side of room):)You were right.
I had nothing to worry about.
(Amy(to Penny, on other side of room):)That skank's your problem, not mine.
- You're very funny, Dr. Hofstadter.
- Oh, thank you.
Agh! Cherry stem. Cherry stem.
(Bernadette:)How you doing, Howie?
You feeling a little better?
(Howard:)Oh. A lot better, thanks. One sec.
(Howard:)Listen close, I don't have a lot of time.
(Howard:)I need you to go to my house.
(Howard:)In my bedroom you'll find a model rocket.
I want you to bring it back to your place.
(Howard:)Okay.
(Howard:)Step two, build a version
roughly 14 stories high.
(Howard:)Fill it full of rocket fuel and come get me.
(Howard:)I'll leave the door unlocked.
(Bernadette:)Maybe you should talk to someone.
(Bernadette:)Let them know
you're having a little anxiety.
(Howard:)No, no. I'm fine. No anxiety.
(Howard:)We should probably talk in code.